[{"question": " you look cute in bubbles.", "answer": " ehh, you're just liquored up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i've had a very long, hard day.", "answer": " ahh, i'm gonna go get some chicken. want some?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " ahh, no thanks. no chicken, bye-bye then.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " you sure? some extra crispy? dirty rice? beans?", "answer": " for the last time no! get out! get out, joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " are you okay? i'm so sorry, he wouldn't leave. he kept asking me about chicken.", "answer": " chicken? i could eat some chicken.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey, pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " mornin' pheebs!", "answer": " i have to tell you this story. okay, i was coming over here and this driver\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " oh, he was this cab driver we had in london.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh. ha-ha-ha. all right, anyway\u009a", "answer": " wait, what that place, that pub he took us too?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " uh, the wheat chief.", "answer": " yeah-yeah-yeah, and they had that beer! that", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " bodington's!", "answer": " bodington's! woohoo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " ooh! ahh, pheebs, was gonna tell a story.", "answer": " yeah, so, he had a really funny hat--i don't want to talk about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hey, ross, bodington's!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " that was good beer.", "answer": " ohh\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " y'know, i'd walk back to london for another frosty one of those bad boys.", "answer": " y'know, i think they have those at that british pub near the trade center.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " isn't rachel supposed to be back by now?", "answer": " yeah, but her plane got delayed in athens. but actually,  she should be here by now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh, so-so you talked to her. did she, did she sound mad?", "answer": " no, but she likes me. you abandoned her on a plane to greece.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " okay, i did not abandon rachel! okay? emily showed up at the airport! i had to go after her! i mean, i-i did what i transfer interrupted! l is my wife! y'know--emily! emily, is my wife! man, what is that?", "answer": " so you still hadn't heard from emily?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " no, not since i lost her at the airport.", "answer": " i can't believe she can out run you man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hey, she's fast!! okay?!!  oh! you-you think you can be beat me? let's go! outside!!", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " rach, rach, i am so sorry. i am so-so sorry.", "answer": " oh ross, come on! you just did what you had to", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " that's it? you're not mad? i mean, it must've been terrible.", "answer": " terrible? hell, i was in greece! that was a nice hotel! nice beach, met the nice people. not to shabby for rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " so, what? that's it?", "answer": " well, yeah! we're cool. totally cool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh no, you're the best.", "answer": "  ohh, i gotta go to the flower store!  check it out, no one will tell me where emily is, so i'm gonna send 72 long-stem, red roses to emily's parent's house, one for each day that i've known and loved her. that oughta get her talking to me again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " rach, that's great! it's so good that you had a good time in greece!", "answer": " what?! i didn't have a good time in greece! ross abandoned me! okay, i couldn't get a plane out, so i had to stay in their honeymoon suite with people coming up to me all the time going, \"oh, mrs. geller, why are you crying?\" i mean, it was sooo humiliating. i felt like such an idiot! i mean, it's all my fault! and you know why, because i make very bad decisions.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh that's not true.", "answer": " yes it is! it is true! i went, i went after ross in stupid london.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " london is stupid! stupid!", "answer": " phoebe, you were right. i should've never gone to london, and from now on you make all of my decisions for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh\u009a no, i did that for someone once and i'm not comfortable having that kind of power and control over someone's life.", "answer": " i'll do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " that's fine. so monica, you are now in control of my love life.", "answer": " okay, i gotta go to work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh, rachel, sweetie, look, here's a really cute picture of joey and you at the reception.", "answer": " ohh, he's married! ross is married. i can't--i still can't believe it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " honey, sweetie, by the edges.", "answer": " i mean, y'know i'm just gonna have to accept it \u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " \u009ai mean it's my fault.", "answer": " sweetie! edges! fingers! smudgey! pictures!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " okay. that's okay. i-i know that you're very upset right now. i know, i know that wasn't about me.", "answer": "  i bet it was about her a little.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " if you would stop thinking about ross for one minute you would notice that there are great guys everywhere! i mean, look! look, gunther!  i mean, he's nice, he's cute.", "answer": " yeah, i guess gunther is kinda\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  oh, what about that guy over there?  remember? that is the guy you flirted with at the counter that time.", "answer": " oh, i don't know. i don't know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " you're going to talk to him! y'know what? we made a deal, i make your decisions and i say you're going to talk to him.", "answer": " all right, you're the boss. i guess i gotta do what you tell me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " hey, pheebs!", "answer": " we got out pictures back from london.  here's all of us at the tower of london.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " all right, y'know what, we've been talking about london too much haven't we?", "answer": " no. i'm sorry. it's just 'cause i couldn't be there. 'cause all i ever get to do now is pregnant stuff, it just bums me out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " what happened?", "answer": " well, y'know, a little of this, a little of that. got myself a date tomorrow night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " see, didn't i tell you?! you're getting over ross already!", "answer": " well\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " what took you so long?", "answer": " i got caught up and work, but i'm quitting tomorrow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  see ya!!  what the hell was that?!", "answer": " probably some y'know, european good-bye thing he picked up in london.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " that's not european!", "answer": " well, it felt french.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh god, i really had a good time!", "answer": " yeah, me too.  so, i guess this is it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah. umm, unless you wanna come inside?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " okay. oh, uh, wait a minute, y'know what? i uh, i can't decide this. umm, okay, just hold on a second.", "answer": " okay, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " umm, hi!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " is monica around? i-i have to ask her something.", "answer": " she's doing her laundry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " it came in the mail today, it's uh, 72 long-stemmed red roses, one for each day that i've known and loved emily, cut up into mulch!", "answer": " oh, honey that's awful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " oh, it's not so bad. monica's gonna make potpourri! i think i'm gonna go wander out in the rain for a while.", "answer": " but, it's not raining.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " i can't catch a break!", "answer": " y'know what ross? you're not going anywhere. you're gonna sit right here. i'm gonna make you a cup of tea and we're gonna talk this thing whole out. all right?  hey, dave!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " umm, listen, i'm gonna need to take a rain check, my roommate is just really sick. okay? bye!  honey, listen, i know, i know things seem so bad right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  rach? can i talk to for just a minute? i-i dropped some socks.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " what is the matter with you?! do you want to fall into the trap? do you want to fall into the trap?!", "answer": " ohh! you did not drop any socks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i just ran into dave and he told me that you blew him off! i mean, you listen to me! now, i'm calling the shots! i say you leave ross alone and go get dave! what the hell were you trying to do?", "answer": " well, ultimately, i was trying y'know, i-i wanted\u009atell him y'know, that i'm still in love with him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  what?!! you cannot tell him that!!", "answer": " why? why not?! people love to hear that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " i make the decisions, and i say no.", "answer": " well, y'know what, no, you do not make my decisions because y'know what, you're fired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " you can't fire me. i make your decisions and i say, \"i'm not fired!\" ha!", "answer": " well\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " rachel!! come on! let me in!", "answer": "  havin' some trouble?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " rachel locked the door.", "answer": " i'll kick that door in if you give me a little sugar. commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " thank you. rachel, can i talk to you outside for a sec?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " i really need to talk to you.", "answer": " well, then talk!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " okay, i will. remember that thing that we just discussed that you wanted to do?", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " what thing?", "answer": " well, rachel wants to take swing dance lessons. which i think is a really stupid idea! it's dangerous, she's never gonna get what she wants, and who knows who she might  end up hurting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " monica's right, swing dancing can be tricky. i'm gonna use the phone. i gotta cancel those five giant teddy bears i sent to emily.  my god, think of the massacre.", "answer": " i'm gonna do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " all right, rachel, i know-i know you think i'm crazy, please, before you tell him you love him, just-just try to find one person who thinks this is a good idea. because i bet you, you can't.", "answer": " but i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " please!", "answer": " all right, fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " joey, i'm in!", "answer": "  all right. good deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " pheebs! hey pheebs!", "answer": " uh, okay, pheebs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " umm, y'know how the other day you were talking about how you didn't get to go to london and how you were kinda feeling left out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " all right, well, we felt really bad about that so we decided we should all take a little trip together!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " ohh, that's so nice! how great! well, where? where's the trip?!", "answer": " well, we thought we would all go to a picnic , in central park!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  central\u009a park!", "answer": " yeah, all of us! all day!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " that sucks! that's not a trip! i just came from the park! what are we gonna high five about at the stupid central park? \"well, it's right by my house, all right!\"", "answer": " well, i'm gonna go home and bask in the triumph of my central park idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": "  hey-whoa-whoa-whoa!! ho-ho-hold on a sec there, mr. kissey! y'know, i've been meaning to talk to you about this whole, little, new european thing you got going on, and i just need to tell you that it makes me very uncomfortable and i just--y'know--stop it!", "answer": " i was just trying to bring a little culture to the group.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " that's fine, just don't bring it in my mouth.", "answer": " makes me wanna puke!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " hey everybody, pheebs is here!", "answer": " phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " hey, pheebs!", "answer": " phoebe, woo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " okay, woo! hi.", "answer": " okay, pheebs, we decided the picnic idea was a little\u009a y'know, it didn't have any\u009a it-it, well it blew. so, we thought, that this afternoon that we would all go away for the whole weekend to, atlantic city!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " ooh, atlantic city! oh, that's a great plan! who's plan was that?", "answer": " mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " wait! it was my plan.", "answer": " nooo, i said we needed a new plan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " and, i came up with atlantic city.", "answer": " which, is the new plan!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " okay, well, why don't we all meet upstairs in an hour?", "answer": " okay! ooh-ahh, i'm gonna go pack. i'm gonna go pack my ass off!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " come on rach, let's go.", "answer": " yeah, y'know what? i'm-i'm gonna meet you upstairs in a minute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " no! rachel, you didn't find anyone so you can't tell him.", "answer": " well, y'know what, that doesn't matter.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " okay, rachel, do you have any idea how painful it is to tell someone that you love them and not have them say it back?", "answer": " yeah, i-i don't care.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " what 'cha readin'?", "answer": " the paper.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " yeah, what's it about?", "answer": " events from around the globe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " okay. uhh, ross, y'know what, there's something that i-that i have to talk to you about and everybody's saying that i shouldn't tell you, but i think they're wrong. i mean, and you know how people can be wrong.", "answer": " sure. once, at work i-i thought carbon dating was fossilized\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " okay, ross, i'm really trying to tell you something here.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " go ahead.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " what? what? was that a joke? 'cause it's mean.", "answer": "  i'm so dead serious. i'm totally serious.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " why are you laughing?", "answer": " because , because, i just heard it. i heard it, and it's ridiculous! i mean, you're married. you're-you're married and it's just ridiculous, and it's like, it's like when said it, i sort of like, i floated up out of my body, y'know? and, and-and then i heard myself say it and then the floating rachel  was like, \"you are such an idiot!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " well, well i am married. even though i haven't spoken to my wife since the wedding.", "answer": "  i'm sorry, that's not funny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " actually, it kinda is. my wife won't return my calls. i don't know where my wife is.  \"hey ross, where's the mrs.?\" don't know!", "answer": " oh god, ohh, okay, y'know what, do you think ah, do you think that you just forget that i told you this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " well, i kinda half to. i mean, because the thing", "answer": " the thing is y'know, that you're married to emily.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " that is what the thing is.", "answer": " ross, things aren't gonna be weird between us, right? i mean was that just the stupidest thing, me telling you that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " no. no. no, i'm-i'm glad you did. look, if nothing else, it's-it's always great when someone tells you they love you.", "answer": " that's what i said! thank you for being so nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " okay, let's go!", "answer": " atlantic city!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " uh, pheebs, you're leaking?", "answer": " oh my god! you're water broke!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " ohh!", "answer": " all right. well, don't worry, i call shotgun!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa! wait-wait!", "answer": " pheebs! we have to take you to the hospital now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " pheebs, pheebs, the babies are coming now.", "answer": " high-five, the babies are coming!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " i can't believe phoebe's gonna have her babies!", "answer": " i know, it's beautiful. amazing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " y'know what else i can't believe? i had to kiss phoebe and rachel every time i left a room, i mean it's too bad they didn't see us having sex.", "answer": " do you know anything about women?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " that's all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep2.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}]